Dmitry Beskov

Tbilisi, Georgia | dmitry.beskov@outlook.com

Work experience

JettyCloud (UCaaS) May 2022 - Now

Software Developer

- Created a chrome extension for the company greatly facilitating the daily work of both QA and development
- Simultaneously worked in several teams and on several projects, never missed deadlines

Created and updated various submodules for client's account pages, internal admin pages

Stack: TS, React&Redux, Java&Kotlin

Foxford (EdTech) December 2020 - May 2022

Frontend developer

- Implemented code review for the team, was an organizer of frontend meetings
- Added large adjustment to the ESLint of a team project, added Stylelint, adjusted bundling and CI of the project
- Optimized JS code of the project and work process of the team developers now are writing faster and more stable code

Practically was a team leader, worked a lot with HTML&CSS and performed managerial activities like teamwork process optimization on various development stages

Stack: JS&FlowType, JQuery, HTML&CSS, React&Effector, NodeJS

BIOS (B2B, startup) April 2019 - December 2020

Software developer

- Web-development: React and Redux / PHP / Typescript / 1C-Bitrix. Maintenence, project development. Self-education, self-refactoring
- System administration: Configuring and deployment of (web-) servers and platforms (1C and others), OS errors resolving, project's git trees management
- Telegram client and TOTP algorithm two-factor authentication development for 1C platform

Was assigned and successfully resolved the most responsible and fundamental tasks, strictly followed the prescribed project timing, found solutions for various business tasks, independently set personal goals for further business improvement

Stack: React&Redux, HTML&CSS, JS, PHP, HTTP, NodeJS, 1C

Education

Saint Petersburg State Electrotechnical University «LETI» 2014 - 2018

«Communication Technologies and Communication Systems»

Faculty of Radio Engineering and Telecommunications

Summary

I'm a React frontend developer. When I work, I usually point out the weak points of the company and can make some suggestions to make our daily work more effective, more fun and/or easier. I also try to fix code issues that I see on a regular basis. I really love what I do and I want to continue to grow in the frontend and to create something great and special.

Technologies and languages I worked with: TypeScript&FlowType, React, Redux&Effector, HTML&CSS, PostgreSQL, Vue, NodeJS, Webpack&Rollup, Gulp, PWA, Browser extensions, jQuery, PHP, Java&Kotlin, YouTrack, Apache, Nginx, 1C, Bash, Python, C++

English (B2): I'm ok with writing and speaking, but I make mistakes sometimes.